Guide to the Steven Bergman Research Files Documenting the School of Management, Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Steven Bergman research files documenting the School of Management, Yale University
1986-1992
RU 914
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.75
The materials, compiled by Steven Bergman, consist of unorganized reports, publications, newspapers, clippings, and photographs documenting the history of the School of Management. The controversy surrounding the appointment of Michael E. Levine as dean of the school in 1988 is particularly well documented.
Bergman, Steven
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 49 (YRG 49), Papers on Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were a gift of Steven Bergman, 2002.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The materials, compiled by Steven Bergman, consist of unorganized reports, publications, newspapers, clippings, and photographs documenting the history of the School of Management. The controversy surrounding the appointment of Michael E. Levine as dean of the school in 1988 is particularly well documented.
Bergman, Steven; Levine, Michael E.; Yale University. School of Management
- Research files of Steven Bergman, Accession 2003-A-029
  - Reports, articles (copies), circa 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 12)
  - Extra copies of SOM archive documents, circa 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Yearbook photographs, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 14 - 17)
  - Correspondence, publications, and news clippings, circa 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 18 - 20)
  - Awareness Week, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 21 - 23)
  - Publications
    - Business Week, 1990 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - US News and World Report, 1992 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Vanity Fair, 1992 August (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Yale Herald, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - New Journal [Yale], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 29 - 30)
    - Yale Record, 1993 May (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Yale Daily News, 1992-1993 (Box 3)
    - New Haven Register, 1992 May (Box 3)
  - "Yale School of Management Scrapbook" [photocopies of news clippings], Circa 1983-1986 (Box 3)